cmtrading.com 2019-01-08

# Privacy Policy | CM Trading

CM Trading places great emphasis on keeping the information shared by our website users and visitors private and confidential. The use of the data you share with us will be governed by the Forex Privacy Policy. Our clients are authorized, licensed and regulated by the Financial Services Board (FSB) of South Africa. CM Trading adheres to the data protection provisions as mentioned in International Law. In order to consider the conditions and threats posed by the changing operations, technologies, practices and legislations, we will review this Policy Statement and update it with required information with/out notification. 

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES CM TRADING COLLECT?**

When you apply for a CM Trading account, we require certain information in order to process the request. This information may include personal and financial details, such as, name, address, contact number, date of birth, employment details, liabilities and assets. 

To improve your trading experience we may require further information. Sometimes the law may require us to hold some information about our customers. In such cases we obtain the information through our application forms and other information request forms. 

**CM TRADING MAY COLLECT THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION**

Personal details (through forms) 

Financial details (through forms and record of services rendered) 

Information about a trader’s usage pattern of our website and trading platforms 

Record of trading activities to help us serve you better 

**HOW DOES CM TRADING USE INFORMATION SHARED BY THE TRADER?**

**The trader information held by CM Trading is used for:**

Creating and handling your account; 

Reviewing your current requirements; 

Enhancing our platforms, services and customer support; 

Providing you with trading advice and information about opportunities. 

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

**On the basis of the product or service concerned and with regard to particular restrictions on sensitive information, CM Trading may disclose information about traders to:**

Specialists, experts, service providers and advisers contracted by us for administrative, insurance, financial research or similar assistance; 

Introducing Brokers (IBs) with whom we share a working relationship; 

Courts, credit providers, tribunals or regulatory authorities authorized by the law; 

Reference or credit reporting agencies; 

Individuals authorized by the trader whose information is being shared. 

If you are not willing to share any information with the mentioned agencies and service providers, please send us a written message. In such a situation, we will withdraw your information from the data pool and consequently withdraw related services. 

**CM TRADING PRIVACY POLICY**

**Updating information** If there is a change in your personal details you may email the updated information to CM Trading at support@CMTrading.com as soon as possible. As per your instructions, CM Trading will update your personal details. However, please note that that the action we take will also need to be consistent with the regulations that govern our data collection and protection practices. Due to our connection with the Global Board of Trade (GBOT) our policies are always in sync with their terms and conditions 

**Use of Cookies** When you open a CM Trading account and access it through your browser, you will need to accept cookies. Cookies or small packets of information received by your computer contain a unique identification number. They are used by our platforms and services for preparing the browser for your use, requirements and preferences. This helps CM Trading to enhance your trading experience when you use our services. Cookies also play an important role in the security of various sections of our online services. You will not be able to view secure parts of the CM Trading website without cookies. 

**Your Rights** Your Rights As per the data protection laws that govern the CM Trading services, all traders are entitled to obtain personal information regarding them from CM Trading and inform us about any inaccuracy perceived. If you wish to make an enquiry, you may email us at support@CMTrading.com. If there are no legal restrictions on sharing the information we will acknowledge and execute your request within 40 days of your request. You might have to incur some the cost of finding, reviewing, and sending across the requested material. 

**Amendments to Policy** CM Trading reserves the right to modify this policy as deemed fit at any time. The latest privacy policy will always be available at this link: https://www.cmtrading.com/en-US/privacy-policy/. 

**Credit Card Processing:** Credit Cards, Debit Cards and some alternative payment methods are processed by CMT PROCESSING LTD, Spyrou Kyprianou Georgiou Griva Digeni, Pamelva Court, 3035, Limassol, Cyprus. Reg. No. HE340325. To contact CMT PROCESSING LTD please call +44 203 318 2176
